Printed Maps Printed.Maps
American Philosophical Society
- North America
  - United States Of America
    - Wyoming
      - Upper Geyser Basin, Fire Hole River, Wyoming Territory. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological and Geographical Survey of the Territories. Surveyed by the party in charge of F. V. Hayden. 1871. Compiled and drawn from field notes and sketches of A. Schönborn by E. Hergesheimer. [Washington]: 1871., 1434; Scale: 1 in. = 550 ft.; Size: 46.9 x 58.6 cm.; F. V. Hayden, A. Schönborn, and E. Hergesheimer.
        Presented by F. V. Hayden, 5 January 1872.
      - Yellowstone Lake. Showing the watershed of the Snake, Madison and Yellowstone Rivers. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological Survey of the Territories. Dr. F. V. Hayden in charge. Surveyed and drawn by Henry W. Elliott. N.p.: 1871., 1435; Scale: 1.1 cm. = 1 mi.; Size: 35.6 x 38.1 cm.; F. V. Hayden and Henry W. Elliott.
        Presented by F. V. Hayden, 6 January 1872.
      - Yellowstone Lake, Wyoming Territory. U.S. Department of the Interior. Surveyed by the party in charge of F. V. Hayden. 1871. N.p.: 1871., 1436; Scale: 1 in. = 2 mi.; Size: 37 x 37.8 cm.; F. V. Hayden, A. Schönborn, E. Hergesheimer, and H. W. Elliott.
      - Yellowstone National Park, from surveys made under the direction of F. V. Hayden. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological Survey of the Territories. 1871. [New York]: J. Bien, lithog.: 1871., 1437; Scale: 1 in. = 10 mi.; Size: 30.2 x 28.3 cm.; F. V. Hayden and E. Hergesheimer.; Julius Bien.
        See: American Journal of Science and Arts, Series 3, Vol. 3, 1872.
        Presented by F. V. Hayden, 15 March 1872.
      - Map of the Lower Geyser Basin on the upper Madison River, after a reconnaissance by Gustavus R. Bechler. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological and Geographical Survey of the Territories. N.p.: [ca. 1876]., 1438; Scale: 6 in. = 1 mi.; Size: 54.7 x 89.6 cm.; Colored.; Gustavus R. Bechler.
      - Map of the Upper Geyser Basin on the upper Madison River, Montana territory, after a reconnaissance by Gustavus R. Bechler. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological and Geographical Survey of the Territories. N.p.: [ca. 1876]., 143; Scale: 6 in. = 1 mi.; Size: 45.4 x 50.3 cm.; Gustavus R. Bechler.
      - Part of central Wyoming. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological and Geographical Survey of the Territories. F. V. Hayden, U.S. Geologist in charge. Surveyed in 1877. New York: Julius Bien: 1877., 1440; Scale: 1:253,440.; Size: 58 x 84.9 cm.; F. V. Hayden and George B. Chittenden.; Julius Bien.
      - Parts of western Wyoming and southeastern Idaho. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological and Geographical Survey of the Territories. Surveyed in 1877 and 1878. F. V. Hayden, in charge. New York: Julius Bien: [1878]., 1877-1878.; 1441; Scale: 1:253,440.; Size: 57.6 x 83.3 cm.; G. R. Bechler, Fred A. Clark, and F. V. Hayden.; Julius Bien.
        Presented by the U.S. Geological and Geographical Survey of the Territories, 7 May 1880.
      - Yellowstone National Park. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological and Geographical Surveys of the Territories. Primary triangulation by A. D. Wilson. Secondary triangulation and topography by Henry Gannett. New York: Julius Bien: 1878., 1442; Scale: 1:126,720.; Size: 81.1 x 72.2 cm.; A. D. Wilson and Henry Gannett.; Julius Bien.
      - State of Wyoming. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1907. Washington: A. B. Graham Co., Litho.: 1907., 1443; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 72.4 x 84.6 cm.; Colored.; A. B. Graham Co.; I. P. Berthrong.
        Insets:Cheyenne and vicinity; Sheridan and vicinity; Evanston; Laramie.
      - State of Wyoming. U.S. Department of the Interior. Lands designated by the Secretary of the Interior as subject to entry under the provisions of the enlarged Homestead Act of February 19, 1909. N.p.: 1911 [1 April 1911]., 1444; Scale: 1 in. = 24 mi.; Size: 36.2 x 42.2 cm.; Colored.; I. P. Berthrong.
        Insets: Sheridan and vicinity; Cheyenne and vicinity; Evanston; Laramie.
      - Panoramic view of the Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming-Montana-Idaho. U.S. Department of the Interior. Prepared by John R. Renshawe. Washington: U.S. Geological Survey: [ca. 1914]., 1445; Scale: 1:187,500.; Size: 52.7 x 46.2 cm.; Colored.; John H. Renshawe.; U.S. Geological Survey.
      - State of Wyoming. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled chiefly from the official records of the General Land Office with supplemental data from other map making agencies under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. Washington: Columbia Planograph Co.: 1923., 1446; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 73.8 x 83.6 cm.; Colored.; I. P. Berthrong and J. J. Black.
    - Idaho
      - State of Idaho. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of Frank Bond. 1905. Washington: Andrew B. Graham Co.: 1905., 1447; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 114.2 x 76.2 cm.; Colored.; Andrew B. Graham Co.; Frank Bond, A. F. Dinsmore, C. J. Helm, and I. P. Berthrong.
        Insets: Pocatello and vicinity; Wallace and vicinity; Lewiston and vicinity; Boise and vicinity.
      - State of Idaho. U.S. Department of the Interior. Lands designated by the Secretary of the Interior as subject to entry under the provisions of the enlarged Homestead Act of June 17, 1910. [Washington]: 1911 [1 April 1911]., 1448; Scale: 1 in. = 24 mi.; Size: 55.5 x 36.4 cm.; Colored.; Charles J. Helm.
    - Utah
      - Atlas accompanying the report on the geology of a portion of the Uinta Mountains and a region of country adjacent thereto. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological and Geographical Survey of the Territories. Second division. By J. W. Powell. 1876. [New York]: J. Bien, lith.: 1876. 2 maps and 6 profiles., 1449; Scale: 4 in. = 1 mi.; Size: ca. 64.3 x 46 cm.; Colored.; S. J. Kübul.; W. H. Graves, J. W. Powell, and G. K. Gilbert.
      - Topographical and geological atlas of the district of the high plateaus of Utah. To accompany the report of Capt. C. E. Dutton. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geographical and Geological Survey of the Rocky Mountain Region. J. W. Powell in charge. New York: Julius Bien: 1879-1880., 145; Size: 96.2 x 73.4 cm; John W. Powell and C. E. Dutton.; Julius Bien
        See: U.S. Geographical and Geological Survey, Report of Clarence Edward Dutton (557.3: Un2ro).
      - State of Utah. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1908. Washington: A. B. Andrews Co.: 1908., 1451; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 85.5 x 66.4 cm.; Colored.; A. B. Andrews Co.; I. P. Berthrong, A. F. Dinsmore, and Wm. Bauman, Jr.
      - State of Utah. U.S. Department of the Interior. Lands designated by the Secretary of the Interior as subject to entry under the provisions of the enlarged Homestead Act of February 19, 1909. [Washington]: 1911 [1 April 1911]., 1452; Scale: 1 in. = 24 mi.; Size: 42.8 x 33.2 cm.; Colored.; A. F. Dinsmore and Wm. Bauman, Jr.
      - State of Utah. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1915. Washington: Eckert Lithographers: 1915., 1453; Scale: 1 in. = 12 statute mi.; Size: 85.1 x 66.8 cm.; Colored.; Eckert Lithographers; I. P. Berthrong, A. F. Dinsmore, Wm. Bauman, Jr., and Thos. O. Wansleben.
    - Arizona
      - Territory of Arizona. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1908. Washington: Norris Peters Company: 1908., 1454; Scale: 1:760,320.; Size: 51.6 x 43 cm; Colored.; I. P. Berthrong and Daniel O'Hare.
        Inset: Southern Arizona and Sonora, Mexico.
      - Territory of Arizona. U.S. Department of the Interior. Lands designated by the Secretary of the Interior as subject to entry under the provisions of the enlarged Homestead Act of February 19, 1909. [Washington]: 1911 [1 April 1911]., 1455; Scale: 1 in. = 24 mi.; Size: 47.6 x 39 cm.; Colored.; Daniel O'Hare and Wm. Bauman, Jr.
        Insets: Tucson; Phoenix; connections to railroads in Arizona.
      - State of Arizona. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and the other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1912. Washington: Eckert Litho. Co.: 1912., 1456; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 95.4 x 78.3 cm.; Colored.; Eckert Litho. Co.; I. P. Berthrong, Daniel O'Hare, and Wm. Bauman, Jr.
        Insets: Connections to railroads in Arizona; Tucson; Phoenix
    - Nevada
      - Topographical map of Washoe mining district, and Outline map of Washoe district, Nevada, showing Comstock Lode.... 1879. New York: J. Bien: [1903]., 1457; Scale: 1:18,000; 1:24,000.; Size: 112.8 x 86 cm.; 87.5 x 64.5 cm.; Colored.
      - State of Nevada. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1908. Washington: Andrew B. Graham Co. lithog.: 1908., 1458; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 109 x 77.5 cm.; Colored.; Andrew B. Graham Co.; I. P. Berthrong, Daniel O'Hare, and Chas. J. Helm.
        Insets: City of Reno; Goldfield and North Goldfield.
      - State of Nevada. U.S. Department of the Interior. Lands designated by the Secretary of the Interior as subject to entry under the provisions of the enlarged Homestead Act of February 19, 1909. [Washington]: 1911 [1 April 1911]., 1459; Scale: 1 in. = 24 mi.; Size: 54.3 x 38.6 cm.; Colored.
      - State of Nevada. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1914. Washington: Eckert Litho. Co.: 1914., 1460; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 108.9 x 77.5 cm; Colored.; Eckert Litho. Co.; I. P. Berthrong and Chas. J. Helm.
        Insets: Reno; Winnemucca; Elko; Ely; Goldfield and Columbia; Tonopah; Carson City.
    - The Northwest
      - United States north west boundary survey. From notes by John G. Parke, U.S. Engineer, Chief Astronomer and Surveyor... exhibiting also surveys and reconnaissances by the British Boundary Commission, U.S. Coast Survey, British Admiralty, U.S. Engineer Bureau; Pacific Rail Road Explorations; U.S. Land Office; Capt. John Paliser; U.S. Exploring Expedition and Lewis and Clark. U.S. Boundary Survey Office. Archibald Campbell U.S. Commissioner. Washington: 1866., 1461; 2 pieces.; Scale: 1:1,000,000.; Size: 40.9 x 61 cm. and 41 x 61 cm.; Colored.; Alexander Gardner; Lemuel D. Williams, Theodor Kolecki, and Edward Freyhold.
        Presented by Archibald Campbell, 20 September 1867.
    - Pacific Coast
      - Reconnaissance of the western coast of the United States from Gray's Harbor to the entrance of Admiralty Inlet. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache, Superintendent. By the hydrographic party under the command of Lieut. James Alden. [Washington]: 1853., 1462; Scale: 1:600,000.; Size: 36.9 x 44.7 cm.; A. D. Bache, James Alden, and E. Hergesheimer.; G. McCoy, E. F. Woodward, and W. Smith.
        Presented through A. D. Bache, 10 October 1854; received 5 January 1855. Contains four scenes of rocks and points.
      - Reconnaissance of the western coast of the United States (middle sheet) from San Francisco to Umpquah River. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache, Superintendent. By the hydrographic party under the command of Lieut. James Alden. Geographical positions by G. Davidson. 1854. [Washington: 1854]., 1463; Scale: 1:1,200,000.; Size: 62 x 56.6 cm.; Colored.; A. D. Bache, James Alden, G. Davidson, W. B. McMurtrie, and A. Lindenkohl.; G. McCoy, J. Knight, J. L. Hazzard, and G. B. Metzeroth.
        Presented through A. D. Bache, 6 March 1857.
        Contains twelve engravings of views along the coast.
      - Reconnaissance of the western coast of the United States (northern sheet) from Umpquah River to the boundary. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache, Superintendent. By the hydrographic party under the command of Lieut. James Alden. Geographical positions by G. Davidson. 1855. [Washington: 1855]., 1464; Scale: 1:1,200,000.; Size: 61.9 x 56.4 cm.; A. D. Bache, James Alden, G. Davidson, W. B. McMurtrie, and A. Lindenkohl.; G. McCoy, J. V. N. Throop, and J. J. Knight.
        Contains eight engravings of headlands, capes, island, rocks and entrance to the Columbia River.
      - Charts of the lights on the Pacific coast of the United States. Published by the order and under the direction of the Light House Board. The coast line prepared from the archives of the U.S. Coast Survey Office. New York: J. Bien: 1861. Series 3 (6 sheets)., 1465; Scale: 1:600,000.; Size of paper: 116.5 x 67 cm.; Colored.; J. Bien.
    - Washington
      - Cape Flattery and Neé-ah Harbor, Washington. U.S. Coast Survey. Topography by G. Davidson. Hydrography by the party under the command of Lieut. James Alden. [Washington]: 1853., 1466; Scale: 1:40,000.; Size: 34.2 x 43.2 cm.; G. Davidson, James Alden, and J. Lambert.; S. Siebert and J. Young.
        Contains engraving of Cape Flattery.
        Presented through A. D. Bache, 10 October 1854; received 5 January 1855.
      - Preliminary survey of Shoalwater Bay, Washington. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache, Superintendent. By the hydrographic party under the command of Lieut. James Alden. 1853. [Washington: 1853]., 1467; Scale: 1:80,000.; Size: 34.3 x 43.6 cm.; A. D. Bache, James Alden, and A. Boschke.; J. Young and S. E. Stull.
      - Reconnaissance of False Dungeness Harbor, Washington. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache, Superintendent. By the hydrographic party under the command of Lieut. James Alden. 1853. [Washington]: 1853., 1468; Scale: 1:30,000; Size: 24.6 x 31.1 cm.; A. D. Bache, James Alden, and J. R. Key.; W. Smith and J. S. Pettit.
      - Reconnaissance of Canal de Haro and Strait of Rosario and approaches, Washington territory. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache, Supdt. Hydrography by the parties under the command of Comdr. J. Alden and R. M. Cuyler. [Washington]. 1858., 1469; Scale: 1:200,000.; Size: 64.4 x 68 cm.; A. D. Bache, J. Alden, R. M. Cuyler, G. Davidson, J. S. Lawson, A. Boschke, J. J. Ricketts, and L. D. Williams.; A. Petersen, R. T. Knight, and E. H. Sipe.
        Inset: Sub sketch of Admiralty Inlet and Puget Sound.
        Presented by Hartman Bache, 21 October 1859.
      - Puget Sound, Washington territory. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. 1867. [Washington]: 1885., 1470; Scale: 1:200,000.; Size: 70.7 x 44.6 cm; James Alden, George Davidson, Charles Wilkes, A. Lindenkohl, and J. S. Lawson.
      - State of Washington. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1909. Washington: Andrew B. Graham Co., litho.: 1909., 1471; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 58.7 x 88.2 cm.; Colored.; Andrew B. Graham Co., litho; I. P. Berthrong, Daniel O'Hare, and Wm. Bauman, Jr.
        Insets: Tacoma; Seattle.
      - State of Washington. U.S. Department of the Interior. Lands designated by the Secretary of the Interior as subject to entry under the provisions of the enlarged Homestead Act of February 19, 1909. [Washington]: 1911 [1 April 1911]., 1472; Scale: 1 in. = 24 mi.; Size: 29.3 x 44.1 cm.; Colored.; Wm. Bauman, Jr.
      - Panoramic view of the Mount Rainier National Park, Washington. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological Survey. Prepared by John H. Renshawe from topographic sheet of the U.S. Geological Survey. [Washington]: U.S. Geological Survey: [ca. 1915]., 1473; Scale: 1:62,500.; Size: 48.6 x 50.7 cm.; Colored.; John H. Renshawe.; U.S. Geological Survey.
    - Oregon
      - Map of the Oregon Territory. By the United States Ex[ploring] Ex[pedition]. Charles Wilkes, Esqr. Commander. 1841. New York: J. H. Young & Sherman & Smith [1841]., 1474; Scale: 1 in. = 51 mi.; Size: 58.8 x 89.2 cm.; Charles Wilkes.; J. H. Young and Sherman & Smith
        Inset: Columbia River, reduced from a survey made by the U. S. Exploring Expedition.
        Presented by J. R. Ingersoll, 3 April 1846.
      - State of Oregon. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1910. Washington: Eckert Litho. Co.: 1910., 1475; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 72.5 x 92.8 cm.; Colored.; Eckert Litho. Co.; I. P. Berthrong, M. Hendges, A. F. Dinsmore, and Wm. Bauman, Jr.
        Inset: City of Portland.
      - State of Oregon. U.S. Department of the Interior. Lands designated by the Secretary of the Interior as subject to entry under the provisions of the enlarged Homestead Act of June 17, 1910. [Washington]: 1911 [1 April 1911]., 1476; Scale: 1 in. = 24 mi.; Size: 35.8 x 46 cm.; Colored.; M. Hendges, A. F. Dinsmore, and Wm. Bauman, Jr.
      - Panoramic view of the Crater Lake National Park, Oregon. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological Survey. Prepared by John H. Renshawe from topographic sheet of the U.S. Geological Survey. Washington: U.S. Geological Survey: [ca. 1913]., 1477; Scale: 1:62,500.; Size: 47.5 x 42.4 cm.; Colored.; John H. Renshawe.; U.S. Geological Survey.
      - Potash from kelp. By Frank Cameron. U.S. Department of Agriculture. Report No. 100, maps. Contribution from the Bureau of Soils. Kelp groves of the Pacific coast and islands of the United States and lower California. Washington: Government Printing Office: 1914., 1478; Scale: 1:200,000 and 1:100,000.; Size: Various.; Colored.
        Contains maps Nos. A-G, 1-2, 4-8, 11-14, 20-21, 23-27, 29-32, 34-47, 49-58, 60-61.
    - California
      - Monterey Harbor, California. U.S. Coast Survey. From a trigonometrical survey under the direction of A. D. Bache. [Washington]: 1852., 1479; Scale: 1:40,000.; Size: 33.5 x 29.7 cm.; A. D. Bache, R. D. Cutts, A. M. Harrison, James Alden, W. B. McMurtrie, and J. Lambert.; S. Siebert, S. V. Hunt, and E. F. Woodward.
        Contains view of Point Pinos.
        Presented through A. D. Bache, 10 October 1854; received 5 January 1855. Presented by the U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey through Spencer C. McCorkle, 14 December 1885.
      - Preliminary sketch of Santa Barbara, California. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache Superintendent. [Washington]: 1853., 1480; Scale: 1:20,000.; Size: 34.4 x 43 cm.; A. D. Bache, A. M. Harrison, James Alden, and J. Lambert.; M. F. O. Strobel, J. Jung, and W. Smith.
        Presented through A. D. Bache, 10 October 1854; received 5 January 1855. Contains: View of the Town and Mission of Santa Barbara.
      - Reconnaissance of the western coast of the United States from San Francisco to San Diego by the hydrographic party under the command of Lieut. James Alden. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache, Superintendent. [Washington]: 1853., 1481; Scale: 1:1,200,000.; Size: 55.8 x 58 cm.; G. McCoy, S. V. Hunt, and W. Smith.; James Alden, W. B. McMurtrie, and W. M. C. Fairfax.
        Contains 17 views of the coast, sailing instructions, tides, etc.
        Presented by Alexander Dallas Bache, 7 March 1857.
      - San Diego entrance and approaches, California. U.S. Coast Survey. From a trigonometrical survey under the direction of A. D. Bache. [Washington]: 1853., 1482; Scale: 1:25,000.; Size: 29.6 x 33.1 cm.; A. D. Bache, R. D. Cutts, Geo. Davidson, A. M. Harrison, and F. Herbst.; S. Siebert, G. McCoy, and E. Yeager.
        Inset: General sketch of San Diego bay and Los Coronados.
      - San Francisco Peninsula. U.S. Coast Survey. Map is reduced from surveys made under the direction of A. D. Bache... by R. D. Cutts. [Washington: 1869]., 1483; Scale: 1:40,000.; Size: 45.7 x 70.6 cm.; A. D. Bache, R. D. Cutts, A. M. Harrison, A. F. Rodgers, and C. Rockwell.
      - Map showing the distribution of Indian tribes of California to illustrate report of Stephen Powers. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geographical and Geological Survey of the Rocky Mountain region: J. W. Powell in charge. [New York]: Julius Bien: 1877., 1484; Scale: 4.5 cm. = 40 mi.; Size: 65.1 x 56.8 cm.; Colored.; H. Lindenkohl, Stephen Powers, and J. W. Powell.; J. Bien.
      - Entrance to San Francisco Bay, California. U.S. Coast Survey. From a trigonometrical survey made under the direction of A. D. Bache. 1859. [Washington]: 1885., 1485; Scale: 1:50,000.; Size: 59.6 x 99 cm.; A. D. Bache, R. D. Cutts, A. F. Rodgers, A. M. Harrison, James Alden, W. M. C. Fairfax, J. Lambert, and J. J. Ricketts.; J. Knight, A. Blondeau, and G. B. Metzeroth.
        Inset: Sub sketch of entrance to San Francisco Bay.
        Contains two views of the entrance to San Francisco Bay.
        Presented by the U. S. Coast and Geodetic Survey through Spencer C. McCorkle, 14 December 1885.
      - Geological map of Shasta county. Prepared for the 11th. report of the State Mineralogist... By H. W. Fairbanks. San Francisco: Britton & Rey: [ca. 1910]., [ca. 1900].; 1486; Scale: 1⅜ in. = 6 mi.; Size: 38.7 x 55.2 cm.; Colored.; Britton & Rey.; H. W. Fairbanks.
      - Pacific coast from Point Pinos to Bodega Head, California. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. Washington: 1903., 1487; Scale: 1:200,000.; Size: 98.5 x 70.6 cm.
      - San Francisco entrance, California. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. Washington: 1903., 1488; Scale: 1:40,000.; Size: 85.5 x 105.6 cm.; Colored.
      - Geological map of the San Francisco Peninsula by Roderic Crandall of the U.S. Coast Survey. Plate no. 1179. 1869. May 1906. [Washington]: 1906., 1489; Scale: 1:40,000.; Size: 70.5 x 45.1 cm.; Colored.and emended by hand.; Roderic Crandall.
      - State of California. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1907. Washington: Andrew B. Graham Co., Litho.: 1907., 1490; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 146.7 x 121.2 cm.; Colored.; Andrew B. Graham Co., Litho.; I. P. Berthrong, A. F. Dinsmore, and Wm. Bauman, Jr.
        Insets: City of Los Angeles; City of San Diego and vicinity; City and county of San Francisco.
      - San Francisco Bay. U.S. Geological Survey. Compiled and engraved and published by the U.S Geological Survey, George Otis Smith, Director. Washington: U.S. Geological Survey: 1914., 1491; Scale: 1:1,000,000.; Size: 46.5 x 56.1 cm.; Colored.; George Otis Smith.; U.S. Geological Survey.
      - Panoramic view of the Yosemite National Park, California. Prepared by John H. Renshawe from the topographic sheet of the U.S. Geological Survey. [Washington]: U.S. Geological Survey: [ca. 1915]., 1492; Scale: 1:187,500.; Size: 45.6 x 47.3 cm.; Colored.; John H. Renshawe.; U.S. Geological Survey.
      - Fault map of the state of California, compiled from data assembled by the Seismological Society of America in cooperation with the Hydrographic Office, Navy Department, the U.S. Geological Survey, the Carnegie Institution of Washington, the University of California and Stanford University. N.p.: [1922]., 1493; 4 sheets.; Scale: 1:506,880.; Size of paper: each ca. 132 x 101.5 cm.; Colored.; Fred B. Scobey, Lot Bowen, John H. Renshawe, Bailey Willis, and H. O. Wood.
      - Geological map of the State of California. Issued by State Mining Bureau. Compiled under the direction of Fletcher Hamilton. 1916. San Francisco: Union Lithograph Co.: 1929., 1494; Scale: 1:823,680.; Size: 147 x 119.3 cm.; Colored.; Fletcher Hamilton and James Perrin Smith.; Union Lithograph Co.
    - Hawaii